Guide to the Stanford University, Public Affairs Office, Records of the Vice President
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Public Affairs Office, records of the Vice President
1962-1981
SC0295
Franklin, H. Bruce (Howard Bruce), 1934-
Stanford University. Public Affairs Office.
22.5 Linear feet
Office files of Robert Rosenzweig, Vice President for Public Affairs,and of his predecessor, Lyle Nelson, Director of University Relations.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Office files of Robert Rosenzweig, Vice President for Public Affairs,and of his predecessor, Lyle Nelson, Director of University Relations.
Access Terms
Nelson, Lyle M.; Rosenzweig, Robert M.; Stanford University. Public Affairs Office.; Stanford University. University Relations.
Collection Contents
- Original accession, 1960-1980
  Correspondence, minutes, memoranda, reports, speeches, and other records, 1960-1980, generated by Robert M. Rosenzweig, Vice President for Public Affairs, and his predecessor Lyle M. Nelson, Director of University Relations. Among the issues covered by these records are the Association of Independent California Colleges and Universities, affirmative action, Stanford Alumni Association, athletics (including Title IX issues), commencement, dedication of various buildings, investments, minorities, and visitors
  Robert M. Rosenzweig was born in Detroit on August 27, 1931. He received his bachelor's degree in political science from the University of Michigan in 1952 and he received his master's degree from the same institution the following year. In 1956, he received his Ph.D. in political science from Yale.
  Rosenzweig joined the Stanford University Staff in 1962 after serving as an instructor at Yale and Amherst, a Congressional Fellow of the American Political Science Association, and special assistant to the United States Commissioner of Education. Rosenzweig started at Stanford a s associate dean of the Graduate Division and a lecturer in political science. In 1967, he was promoted to associate provosr by President Wallace Sterling. During this time (1967- 68), Rosenzweig also served as the director for the Center for Researcll in International Studies. In May 1971, he was named vice-provost and advisor to President Richard W. Lyman. He held this position until December 1974, when he became the first vice-president of public affairs. His duties in this position included responsibility for Stanford 's federal, state and community government relations, news and public services, public event programs, and other public affairs activities.
  During his time at Stanford, Rosenzweig was a consultant on international programs to the Ford Foundation and he represented Stanford within the Association of Independent California Colleges and Universities (AICCU). In 1978, he was elec ted vice -president of the AICCU and in 1980, he was elected president. He was also a member of the Committee on International Studies and the Committee of Fifteen, a joint student-faculty administration group, an d he was a director of the Far West Laboratory for Educational Research and Development.
  In 1983, Rosenzweig left Stanford to head the As s ociation of American Universities (AAU) in Washington, D.C.
  Rosenzweig is married and has two children.
  - AAU (American Association of Universities), 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AAU, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AAU, beginning 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AAU Advisory Committee on the National Science Foundation (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - AAU Evaluation, Oct. 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AAUP (American Association of University Professo rs), 1964-1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - AAUP, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - ABC (A Better Chance)! Proposal, Aug. Harch 1974, 1973- (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - ABC, 1974-75 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ACE (American Council on Education), beginning 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - AICCU (Association of Independent California Colleges and Universities), 1972-73 Academic year (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AICCU 1974-75 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - AICCU 1975-76 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - AICCU 1976-77 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - AICCU March 15, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - AICCU 1977-78 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - AICCU beginning 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - AICCU: Budget Committee; RHL Chairman (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - AICCU: Conference Liaison Committee (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - AICCU: Ford Study (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - AICCU (Executive Committee), Harriott Hotel (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - ASSU Film Series: Hestern Politico, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - ASSU: General, 1971-78 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - ASSU Miscellaneous, 1967-70 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - ASSU Task Force on Tenure and Teaching Quality (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Academic Council, 1962-74 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Academic Information Center (AIC), 1970-73 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Academic Planning Office, 1971 -73 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Academic Research, 1969-70 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Academic Senate, 1968 - 70 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Action, 1971-73 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Action Research Liaison Office, beginning J uly 25, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Administrative, Guided, 1975-80 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Lackeys, 197 2-78 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Searches (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Admissions (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Admissions, 1972-74 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Admissions: General, 1968-72 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Admissions: Minority (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Admissions: Preferred (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Admissions Seminar, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Adult Education Proposal, 1968-71 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Advanced Management College, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Advising (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Affirmative Action Progr am, 1970-74 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Affirmative Action Pro gram, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Affirmative Action Program, 1973-77 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Affirmat ive Action, Sept. 1977-Dec. 1980 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Affirmative Action Annual Report, April 1978 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Affirmative Action Annual Report, May 1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Affirmative Ac tion: Ad Hoc Committee of Af fi rmative Action (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Affirmative Action: Backgr ound Informat i on (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Affirma tive Ac tion: Handicapped (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Affirmative Action for Women (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Affirma tive Action Plan for Stanford University (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Affirmative Action Program (RFB) Res earch, 1979- 80 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Affirmative Action Search (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - African and Afro-American Studies, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Albers: Joseph Albers Sculpture, 1976-78 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Alumni: Alumni Leadership Conference, 1970-71 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Alumni: General File, 1970-72 and 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Almanac, 1967-71 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Almanac, 1969-71 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Assoc iation, 1973-77 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Association, 1974-77 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Association, 1977-78 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Association: Campus Conference, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Association: Campus Conference, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Association: Campus Conference, 1971-73 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Association: Class Reunions, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Association: Conferences, 1970-72 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Association: Executive Board, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Association: Executive Board, 1975-7 7 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Association: Executive Board, beginning, Sept. 1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Association: Executive Board, beginning 19 7: (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Association: Executive Board Meetings, Curren t (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Associa tion: Executive Board Minutes, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Association: Executive Board Mee ting, May I ' (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Association: Executive Board Meeting, Oct. 1970 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Association: Executive Board Meetings, 1972-74 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Alumni Association: Executive Board Meeting, 27432 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Alumni Association: Executive Board Meeting, Oct. 23-25, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Alumni Associa tion: General, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Alumni Association: Hawaii Conference, 1970-71 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Alumni Association: Opinion Survey, 1971-72 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Alumni Associat ion: ROTC Commission (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Alumni Association: San Diego Conference, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Alumni Associa tion: Sierra Camp, 1973-74 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Alumni Association: Stanford Clubs, 1969-72 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Alumni Association: Summer Alumni College, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Alumni Association: Trustee Nomination Committee, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Alumni Day Colleges, 1975-76 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Alumnus Guest-in-Residence, 1970-71 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - American Alumni Council, 1965-69 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - American Association of Fund Raising Counsel, 196 4-1970 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - American Association for Higher Education, 1972-74 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - American Federation of Teachers, 1967-68 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Amherst Le tter, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Anniversaries - Retirements, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Annual Fund, 1966-73 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Anti-Riot Riders Memos (Government Regulations) (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Anti-Trust Issues, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - April 3rd Movement, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Arms Control (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Arms Control, 1972-73 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament, 1973-74 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament, 1974-75 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Arms Control, 1976-77 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Arms Control, 1977-78 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Arms Control, 1978-79 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Art and Architecture: Program at Stanford, etc., 1961-72 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Art and Architecture: Hanna House (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Art Building - Nathan Cummings, 1967-72 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Articles for Newspapers and Magazines by Stanford Faculty, 1960-69 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Artificial Intelligence Laboratory, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Arts and Humanities: General, 1965-72 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Arts and Humanities: Washington International Arts Le tter, 1969-71 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Ass ociation of American Colleges (AAC), 1969-74 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1974-75 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Athletic Board: Athletics (P.E. and Recreation ) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Athletic Director Search, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Athletics: Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - NCAA Title IX Policy Interpretation (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - HEW Final Title IX Re gulation Implementing Education Amendments of 1972 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Title IX - Compliance Revi ew (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Title IX - Financial (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Title IX - Legislation, 1975-78 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Title IX - Phoenix Meeting, Oct. 3-4, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - De Hart Associates, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Department of Justice Comments on the Civil Righ t s Division on Prop. Policy Interpretation (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Comments from Ot her Institutions re: Title IX (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Baccalaureate, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Balance of Trade, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Band, 1974-75 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Band on Campus: Wells Far go, 1972-73 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Bay Area Council, 1967-72 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Bechtel International Student Center, 1968-78 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Bicentennial, 1972- 75 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Biological Sciences: Center, Human Biology Progran (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Black Affairs, 1972-78 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Black Student Union, 1969 - 71 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - B'nai B'rith Hillil Foundation (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Board of Trustees, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting: SDS Disruption, 25217 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Board of Trustees: Committees (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Board of Trustees: Faculty Student Advisory Committee (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Bombing (Robert Nelson), 1971 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Bookstore, 1979-80 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Brown, Edmund G., J r. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Brussels, Belgium; 1971-73 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Brussels Conference, 1971-73 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Buck Club, 1965-73 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Buckley Amendment (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Budget: Federal, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Budget: HEW, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Budget: National (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Budget: National; Office of Management and Budget (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Budget: Presidential Commission on University Budget Priorities (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Budget: Stanford, 1972-75 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Budget: Stanford, 1976-78 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Business and Finance Office, 1971-72 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Business Office, beginning 1970 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Business School, beginning 1971 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Business School, 1972-74 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Butler, Lewis H., 1969-70 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - California, University of, 1969-72 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - California, University of: Academic Administration Internship Program (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - California, University of, Berkeley: Tuition Battle, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Cambodia Issue, beginning May 31, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Cambodia Issue, beginning June 1, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Camp Lectures, 1970-77 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Campaign, 1975-77 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Campaign for Stanford, April 11, 1972-Dec. 1974 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Campus Judicial Hearing Officers, 1970-71 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Campus Report (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Campus Report, 1968-71 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Campus Unres t: Segis1ation, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Cap and Gown Society, 1963-69 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Career Planning and Placement Center (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Career Planning and Placement Center, 1973-74 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Carnegie Foundation, 1970-74 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Carter and Company (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Science, 1966-74 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Center for Research in International Studies (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Chicago, University of: General, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Chicago 7 Protests, beginning Feb. 1970 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Chicano Affairs (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Child Care Center, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Children's Health Council, 1969-72 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Children's Hospital Rehabilitation Center, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Chinese Ping Pong Team Visit, Spring 1972 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Church, Sen. Frank, 1965-70 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Clearinghouse on Educational Media and Technology, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Cohelan, Congo Jeffery, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - College Guide Books: General, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Commencement, 1962-63 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Commencement, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Commencement, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Commencement, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Commencement, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Commencement, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Commencement, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Commencement, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Commencement, 1979-80 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Commencement, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Revision Committee, 1964- 65 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Athletics (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Committees, 1972-73 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Committee for Corporate Support for American Universities (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Economic Development, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Emergency Committee on Full Funding, 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Sub-committee on Evaluation of Teaching (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Committee of Fifteen (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Foreign Study Programs, 1973-74 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Foreign Study Programs, 1974-76 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Committee on Foreign Study Programs (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Committee on Governmental Relat ions, 1963-70 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Committee on Governmental Relations, beginning, Jan. 1971 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Governmental Relations (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Committee on Health Policy (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Ad Hoc Task Force on University Hospital Salary Relationship (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Committee on Land and Building Development, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Committee to Review the Office of Ass istant to the President for Chicano Affairs (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - University Committee on Services to Students (COSS ) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Student Participation in the Political Process, 1970-71 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Committees at Stanford (Members), 1970 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Common Cause (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Communication (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Communication, Department of (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Community Relations (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Complaint Let ters Survey, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Complaints (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Computer Technology: Use and Ramifications (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Computa tion Center: General File, 1970-73 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Conference Center (Harrison), 1978-79 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Conferences/Seminars/Centers (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Conferences/Seminars, 1969-71 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Conferences on Campus, 19 73-74 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Conference at C1iveden on Europe (Summer 1976) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Conference, L.A., 1977-78 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Issues of the' 80s Conferences, Oct. 20, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Science Writ ers Conference, Sept. 4-9, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Congressional Fellowship Program (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Congressional Record Digest, 1966-67 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Const itution Revision: California State Sales Tax, Government Property, 1969-73 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Convocati on (Pitzer Era), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Coordination Council for Higher Education, 1968-73 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Cornell University: General File, 1969-72 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Corporate File (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Corporate Investments Controversy, 1970-72 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Corporate Responsibility, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Corporat e Responsibility: Corres po ndence and I nf ormation, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Cowell Student Health Ser vice, 1963-72 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Cox, Archibald, 1973-74 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - CROW (Center for Research on Women) 1974-78 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Davidson, Ralph, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Day Colleges, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Dean of Student Affairs Office, beginning 19 76 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Deans' Retreat, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Debate (Competition, etc.), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Dedications: Bing Nursery School, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Dedications: Deguerre Pools and Courts (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Dedications: Earth Sciences Building, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Dedications: Food Research Ins titute, 19 70 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Dedications: Graham Stuart Reception, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Dedications: Maples Pavillion, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Dedications: McCullough Building, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Dedications: Pierce Mitchell, April 30, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Dedications: Solar Observatory, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Development: Materials (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Development: Of f ice of Vice President (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Dogs, 1969-73 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Earth Sciences, 1967-72 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - East Asian Studies, 1971-74 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - East Asian Studi es (with D.C. Berkeley), Asian American Studies (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Ecology/Earth Day, 1963-70 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Economic Stabilization Program, begi nni ng Aug. 197J (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Education: Coordinating Council for Highe r Education, 1963-69 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Education: Eurich Study of Education, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Education, School of, 1966-75 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Education, School of: Center for Research and Development in Teaching, 1970-72 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Education: Study of Education at Stanford (SES), 1962-72 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Education: SES Steer ing Committee, 1967-68 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Education: Study of Graduate Education at Stanf ord (SGES), beginning 1972 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Education: D. S. Commissioner of Ed ucation, 1965-- 67 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Education and Labor Committee, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Education and World Affairs: Intercultur al Edu cation, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Education Staff Seminar, 1973-74 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Educational Opportunity Grants (EOG), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Ehrlich, Professor Paul, 1977-78 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Election, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Ellington, Duke, April 1974 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Employment at Stanford: Hinority Affairs, etc., 1968-71 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Encina Fire, June 1972 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Endowed Professorships, Inaugurations, etc., 1963-7 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Energy Crisis, 1973-75 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Energy Research and Development Administration (ERr (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Engineering, School of, 1967- 78 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - English Department, 1969-73 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Envirommental Agency, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Etzioni, Professor Amitai, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Evaluation of Teaching, 1972-78 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Exchange Programs, 1978-79 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - External Publications, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Extermal Publications Task Force, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Externships (Stanford-in-Business), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Extra Departmental Programs, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Facility Planning, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Faculty Club, 1963-77 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Faculty and Staff: Other Universities, 1964-72 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Federal Aid to Higher Educa tion, 1969-71 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Federal Aid to Higher Education: Correspondence, 1969-73 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Federal Aid t o Higher Education: Harvard Meeting, Aug. 20-21, 19 71 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Federal Officials, 1969-71 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Federal Tax Reform, 1970-72 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Federal Tax Reform, through Dec. 1969 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Fellows of the University, 1968-72 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Filer Commission, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Finance, Department of - Frank Bowen, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Financial Aid Changes, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Financial Aid for Students, 1974-82 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Financial Crisis - Bail Out, 1970- 72 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Financing Higher Education, 1972-74 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Financing Higher Education: ACA 47 Constitution Revision (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Financing Research, 1968- 71 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Finch, Robert H., 19 70 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Paul Flory Dinner, Jan. 13, 19 75 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Food Resear ch Institute, 1967-72 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Food Service Advisory Committee, 1968-73 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Football
    - Food Stamp Program, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Football a t Stanford (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Football File, 1976- 77 (Box 10, Folder 16)